Finding aid for Mike Wallace CBS/60 Minutes Papers, 1922-2007
Bentley Historical Library
- 60 Minutes Program Files
  - Season X, September 1977-September 1978
    - "Crime...and Very Little Punishment" (juvenile crime), December 18, 1977
      - Transcript (Box 10)
    - "Judy" repeat (original air date: August 3, 1975), Transcript, December 25, 1977 (Box 10)
    - "Vladimir Horowitz" (profile of the famed pianist), Background/Post-Show (no transcript; see repeat, 4/30/78), December 26, 1977 (Box 10)
    - "This Year at Murrieta" (California health spa's claim of cancer cure), January 1, 1978
      - Background (Box 10)
      - Post-Show (Box 10)
      - Transcript (Box 10)
    - "The USA vs. Judge Ritter (Chief Federal Judge in Salt Lake City, who has most of his rulings overturned), January 8, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 10)
      - Transcript (Box 10)
    - "How to Succeed..." (the Mirage Tavern front, and corruption among city officials in Chicago;), January 15, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 10)
      - Transcript (Box 10)
    - "Lights, Camera...Altman" (interview with Robert Altman), January 22, 1978
      - Background (Box 10)
      - Transcript (Box 10)
    - "L.N.G." (the dangers of transporting liquid natural gas), January 29, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 10)
      - Transcript (Box 10)
    - "Perks" (corporate benefits and discounts for executives), February 5, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "Begin" (profile of Israeli Prime Minister Menachem Begin), February 12, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "Linda Velzy is Dead" (murder of a hitchhiking Oneonta College student), February 19, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "Why Can't Johnny Read?" (failures of the public school system and an interview with maverick New York City teacher and principal Howard Hurwitz), February 26, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "Power Thieves" (people who obtain electricity illegally and without paying for it), March 5, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "Sadat" (profile of Egyptian President Anwar el-Sadat), March 12, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces a story and reads mail), March 19, 1978 (Box 11)
    - "Terror International" (an alliance of international terrorists), April 9, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "The $4 Billion Lunch" (new school lunch programs), April 16, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "A Better Idea" (companies, including the Raymond Lee Organization, that promise to market new inventions), April 23, 1978
      - Background (Box 11)
      - Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "Vladimir Horowitz" repeat (original air date: December 26, 1977), Transcript, April 30, 1978 (Box 11)
    - "The Secret War" (former CIA agent Frank Snepp on Cuban troops in Africa), May 7, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "Wm. Colby" (interview with former CIA Director William Colby), May 14, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 11)
      - Transcript (Box 11)
    - "Crime...and Very Little Punishment" repeat (original air date: December 18, 1977), Transcript, May 21, 1978 (Box 11)
    - "Grief" repeat (original air date: February 29, 1976), Transcript, May 28, 1978 (Box 11)
    - "Why Can't Johnny Read?" repeat (original air date: February 26, 1978), Transcript, June 4, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "Is Your Car Safe?" (safety of the Ford Pinto), June 11, 1978
      - Background (Box 12)
      - Post-Show (Box 12)
      - Transcript (Box 12)
    - "The $7 Misunderstanding" (controversial land deal in Alaska), June 18, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 12)
      - Transcript (Box 12)
    - "How to Succeed..." repeat (original air date: January 15, 1978); "Bon Voyage" repeat (original air date: December 11, 1977), Background/Postshow/Transcript, June 25, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "The Buttleggers" repeat (original air date: September 25, 1977); "Warning: Microwave Radiation" repeat (original air date: June 19, 1977), Background/Transcript, July 2, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "Con Game" repeat Background/Transcript (original air date: December 4, 1977), July 9, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "Kidnapping Italian Style" repeat (original air date: January 16, 1977), Background/Transcript, July 16, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "What Makes Fritz Run?" repeat (original air date: November 27, 1977), Background, July 23, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "Valium" repeat (original air date: October 9, 1977), Background/Transcript, July 30, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "Mixed Marriages" repeat Background/Transcript (original air date: October 16, 1977), August 6, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "Ghost Surgery" repeat (original air date: February 27, 1977), Transcript, August 13, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "Angel Dust/PCP" repeat (original air date: October 23, 1977), Transcript, August 20, 1977 (Box 12)
    - "A Matter of Degrees" repeat (original air date: April 2, 1978), Transcript, August 27, 1978 (Box W3)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces a story), September 3, 1978 (Box 12)
    - "This Year at Murrieta" repeat (original air date: January 1, 1978), Transcript, September 10, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Season XI, September 1978-September 1979
    - "The Rating Game" (television ratings), September 17, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 12)
      - Transcript (Box 12)
    - "The Thorpe Affair" (scandal involving Jeremy Thorpe, former Liberal Party leader in Great Britain), September 24, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 12)
      - Transcript (Box 12)
    - "Palestinian/American" (Americans of Palestinian descent), October 1, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 12)
      - Transcript (Box 12)
    - "GLACAA" (how tax money is spent on the Greater Los Angeles Community Action Agency), October 8, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 12)
      - Transcript (Box 12)
    - "Lord Lew of Show Biz" (British impresario Lew Grade), October 15, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 12)
      - Transcript (Box 12)
    - "Brother Roloff" (Reverend Lester Roloff, who runs controversial homes for wayward children), October 22, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 12)
      - Transcript (Box 12)
    - "Vigilantes" (profile of Anthony Imperiale, founder of the North Ward Citizens Committee, Newark, NJ), October 29, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Putting Out the Fire" (privately owned fire department in Scottsdale, Arizona), November 5, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Iran" (current political troubles), November 12, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Roman Polanski" (interview), November 19, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Do You 'Take' This Man...?" (what happens to savings and property when unmarried couples separate), November 26, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "From Burgers To Bankruptcy" (people who invested in Wild Bill's fast food restaurant and lost their money), December 3, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Fat... And Proud of It" (the National Association to Aid Fat Americans (NAAFA) Convention), December 10, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Minority Fronts" (construction companies using minorities to be eligible for government funding), December 17, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "I'm an American" (Ted Morgan, former French aristocrat who became an American citizen), December 31, 1978
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Another Elvis?" (Nashville record companies that take advantage of undiscovered singers), January 7, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Paper Blizzard" (the amount of government paperwork in small businesses), January 14, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Soak the Poor" (how the poor pay more for industrial (life) insurance), January 28, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 13)
      - Transcript (Box 13)
    - "Protecting the Witness" (the witness relocation program), February 4, 1979)
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 14)
      - Transcript (Box 14)
    - "The Rat" (the worldwide rat problem), February 11, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 14)
      - Transcript (Box 14)
    - "Misha" (profile of Mikhail Baryshnikov), February 18, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 14)
      - Transcript (Box 14)
    - "Our Secret Army" (the 'secret army' in Indochina which America has abandoned; Hmong refugees escaping Laos; boat people), March 4, 1979
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Post-Show (Box 14)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories: Wallace does Point-Counterpoint, Letters), March 11, 1979 (Box 14)
    - "Arafat" (interview with Yasser Arafat), March 18, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 14)
      - Transcript (Box 14)
    - "The Chief Justice" (profile of Supreme Court Chief Justice Warren Burger), March 25, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Transcript (Box 14)
    - "Vanessa" (profile of Vanessa Redgrave), April 1, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 14)
      - Transcript (Box 14)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories: Wallace does Point-Counterpoint, Letters), April 8, 1979 (Box 14)
    - "God and Mammon" (investigation of financial irregularities in the Worldwide Church of God), April 15, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Transcript (Box 14)
    - "Chiropractors" (the chiropractic profession), April 22, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 15)
      - Transcript (Box 15)
    - "Here's...Johnny" (interview with Johnny Carson), April 29, 1979
      - Press (Box 15)
      - Transcript (Box 15)
    - "The Thorpe Affair" repeat (original air date: September 24, 1978), Transcript, May 6, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Minority Fronts" repeat (original air date: December 17, 1978), Transcript, May 20, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Vigilantes" repeat (original air date: October 29, 1978), Transcript, May 27, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Brother Roloff" repeat (original air date: October 22, 1978), Transcript, June 3, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Andy Rooney and reads mail), June 10, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Protecting the Witness" repeat (original air date: February 4, 1979), Transcript, June 17, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Ed Bradley story, Andy Rooney, and reads mail), June 24, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Our Secret Army" repeat (original air date: March 4, 1979), Transcript, July 1, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Andy Rooney), July 8, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Do You 'Take' This Man...?" repeat (original air date: November 26, 1978), Transcript, July 15, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Lord Lew of Show Biz" repeat (original air date: October 15, 1978), Transcript, July 22, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Misha" repeat (original air date: February 18, 1979), Transcript, July 29, 1979 (Box 15)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Harry Reasoner story), August 5, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Another Elvis?" repeat (original air date: January 7, 1979), Transcript, August 12, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Vanessa" repeat (original air date: April 1, 1979); "Vanessa & Fania" (interview with Vanessa Redgrave and Fania Fenelon, whom Redgrave portrays in a television program on the Holocaust), Transcript, August 19, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "Chiropractors" repeat (original air date: April 22, 1979), Transcript, August 26, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "GLACAA" repeat (original air date: October 8, 1978), September 9, 1979
      - Transcript (Box 15)
      - Update Materials, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Season XII, September 1979-September 1980
    - "On Trial For Murder" (Dr. William Waddill, accused of murdering an abortion-delivered fetus), September 16, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 15)
      - Transcript (Box 15)
    - "Here's...Johnny" repeat/update (original air date: April 29, 1979), September 23, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 15)
      - Transcript (Box 15)
    - "Northern Ireland,", September 30, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Transcript (Box 15)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Andy Rooney, reads mail), October 7, 1979 (Box 15)
    - "The Stolen Cezannes" (how easy it is to steal and sell great art works), October 14, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 15)
      - Transcript (Box 15)
    - "Edward Rubin, M.D." (perhaps the largest case of Medicaid fraud in history), October 21, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Transcript (Box 15)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Andy Rooney, reads mail), October 28, 1979 (Box 16)
    - "Swine Flu" (problems resulting from the swine flu immunization program), November 4, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 16)
      - Transcript (Box 16)
    - "Looking Back" (three veterans who were critically wounded in Vietnam), November 11, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 16)
      - Transcript (Box 16)
    - "The Ayatollah" (interview with the Ayatollah Khomeini of Iran), November 18, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 16)
      - Transcript (Box 16)
    - "Roy Innis" (Director of CORE, accused of systematic looting of CORE funds for personal benefit), November 25, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Transcript (Box 16)
    - "The Brethren" (Bob Woodward's book on the Supreme Court), December 2, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 16)
      - Transcript (Box 16)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Harry Reasoner story, reads mail), December 9, 1979 (Box 16)
    - "The Hooker Memos" (alleged industrial pollution by the Hooker Chemical Company), December 16, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 16)
      - Transcript (Box 16)
    - "The Sheik" (interview with Saudi Arabia's Oil Minister Zaki Yamani), December 23, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 16)
      - Transcript (Box 16)
    - "Big John" (interview with Presidential Contender John Connally), December 30, 1979
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 16)
      - Transcript (Box 16)
    - "B.M.O.C." (profile of John Silber, President of Boston University), January 6, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 16)
      - Transcript (Box 16)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Andy Rooney), January 13, 1980 (Box 16)
    - "Bette Davis" (profile), January 20, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 17)
      - Transcript (Box 17)
    - "Russian Spies in the USA" (Soviet spies working undercover in the United States), January 27, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 17)
      - Transcript (Box 17)
    - "Ezer" (interview with Israeli Defense Minister Ezer Weizman), February 3, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Transcript (Box 17)
    - "Lenny" (profile of conductor Leonard Bernstein), February 10, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Transcript (Box 17)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Andy Rooney and reads mail), February 24, 1980 (Box 17)
    - "The Iran File" (investigation of the brutalities and corruption in Iran under the deposed Shah and the alleged United States complicity in those crimes), March 2, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 4 folders (Box 17)
      - Transcript (Box 17)
    - "Oman" (profile of the country), March 9, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 17)
      - Transcript (Box 17)
    - "Blood Money" (alleged fraud in fundraising by Stephen Blood for the Southern Christian Leadership Conference), Background/Post-Show, March 16, 1980 (Box 17)
    - "The Riddle of DMSO" (the controversial drug dimethyl sulfoxide), March 23, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Transcript (Box 18)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Andy Rooney and reads mail), March 30, 1980 (Box 18)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Dan Rather story and reads mail), April 6, 1980 (Box W3)
    - "Scientology: The Clearwater Conspiracy" (alleged crimes committed by members of the Church of Scientology in Clearwater, Florida) (no transcript; see repeat ("Scientology"), August 31, 1980), April 13, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 18)
    - "Israeli Arms for Sale" (the Israeli arms production industry), April 13, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 18)
    - "Omega 7" (a clandestine group of anti-Castro Cuban terrorists operating in the United States), April 20, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Transcript (Box 18)
    - "Here's...Johnny" repeat (original air date: September 23, 1979), Transcript, April 27, 1980 (Box 18)
    - "Not to My Kid, You Don't" repeat (original air date: November 14, 1971), May 4, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 18)
      - Transcript (Box 18)
    - "Bonnie" (profile of Bonnie Consolo, born without arms), May 11, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 18)
      - Transcript (Box 18)
    - "Memory of Vietnam" repeat (original air date, as "Looking Back": November 11, 1979), Transcript, May 25, 1980 (Box 18)
    - Summer Repeats, 1980 (Box 18)
    - "This Year at Marienbad" repeat (original air date: July 14, 1974), Transcript, June 1, 1980 (Box 18)
    - "God and Mammon" update (original air date: April 15, 1979), Transcript, June 8, 1980 (Box 18)
    - "What Johnny Can't Read" (Texans Norma and Mel Gabler's crusade to clean up textbooks), June 15, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 18)
      - Transcript (Box 18)
    - "Death of the Backlot" update (original air date: November 26, 1972), June 29, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 18)
      - Transcript (Box 18)
    - "The Riddle of DMSO" update (original air date: March 23, 1980), July 6, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 18)
      - Transcript (Box 18)
    - Transcript (Wallace corrects error in story), July 13, 1980 (Box 18)
    - "First Family of the GOP" (interviews with Ronald and Nancy Reagan and daughters Patricia and Maureen), July 14, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - "What Makes Fritz Run?" repeat (original air date: November 27, 1977), July 20, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - "Bette Davis" repeat (original air date: January 20, 1980), July 27, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - "The Castle Bank Caper" update (original air date: November 21, 1976), August 3, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - "Oman" repeat (original air date: March 9, 1980), Background/Post-Show/Transcript, August 24, 1980 (Box 19)
    - "Scientology" repeat (original air date: April 13, 1980), Background/Post-Show/Transcript, August 31, 1980 (Box W3)
    - "Edward Rubin, MD" repeat (original air date: October 21, 1979), Transcript, September 7, 1980 (Box 19)
    - "GLACAA" repeat (original air date: October 8, 1978), Transcript, September 14, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Season XIII, September 1980-September 1981
    - "On the Waterfront" (labor racketeering on the Miami, Florida docks), September 21, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - "The $77,000 Bill" (charges of wastefulness and inefficiency in the Medicare administration), September 28, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace introduces Andy Rooney and reads mail), October 5, 1980 (Box 19)
    - "Rational Suicide?" (the controversial issue of suicide as a plausible option for the terminally ill), October 12, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 3 folders (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - "Artie" (profile of columnist Art Buchwald), October 19, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - "Little Abscam" (small time corruption and possible entrapment by the FBI in Kentucky), October 26, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - "Teamster Violence" (allegations of arson, vandalism and violence by teamsters attempting to unionize non-union companies), November 2, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 19)
      - Transcript (Box 19)
    - "Chemical Warfare" (comparison of the preparation for chemical warfare in the United States and the Soviet Union), November 16, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Transcript (Box 20)
    - "The IBM Caper" (the big business of stolen office equipment), November 23, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 20)
      - Transcript (Box 20)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace's update from Teheran, on the American hostages and the Iran-Iraq war), November 30, 1980 (Box 20)
    - "'We're in the Money'?" (the questionable bookkeeping practices in Hollywood), December 7, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 20)
      - Transcript (Box 20)
    - "Iran, December 1980", December 14, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Transcript (Box 20)
    - "Itzhak" (profile of violinist Itzhak Perlman), December 21, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 20)
      - Transcript (Box 20)
    - "Ashes to Ashes" (cremation), December 28, 1980
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 20)
      - Transcript (Box 20)
    - "The Last Mafioso" (transcript only), January 4, 1981 (Box W3)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace reads mail), January 11, 1981 (Box 20)
    - "Patti" repeat (interview with Patti Davis; original air date: July 14, 1980 as part of "First Family of the GOP"), Background/Post-Show/Transcript, January 18, 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 20)
    - "Hartz Mountain" (allegations of questionable business practices by the Hartz Mountain pet supply corporation), February 1, 1981
      - Background, 3 folders (Box 20)
      - Post-Show (Box 20)
      - Transcript (Box 20)
    - "Time Bomb" (Huntington's disease), February 8, 1981
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 20)
      - Transcript (Box 20)
    - "...By What It Will Do To the Arabs" (Israeli Arabs), February 15, 1981
      - Background (Box 21)
      - Stone-Throwing Controversy (Box 21)
      - Harassment and Security (Box 21)
      - Post-Show (Box 21)
      - Transcript (Box 21)
    - "The Minister of Cocaine" (government officials involved in the cocaine business in Bolivia), March 1, 1981
      - Background (Box 21)
      - Post-Show (Box 21)
      - Transcript (Box W3)
    - "Killer Wheels" (accidents involving multi-piece truck and bus tire rims), March 8, 1981
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 21)
      - Transcript (Box 21)
    - "Easy Money" (allegations of fraud in small business loan companies), March 15, 1981
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 21)
      - Transcript (Box 21)
    - Transcript (no Mike Wallace stories; Wallace reads mail), March 22, 1981 (Box 21)
    - "Collision" (politics and air traffic safety), March 29, 1981
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Post-Show (Box 21)
      - Transcript (Box 21)
    - "Sting Man" (interview with Abscam con man and self-confessed swindler Melvin Weinberg), April 12, 1981
      - Background/Post-Show (Box 21)
      - Transcript (Box 21)